<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Experience on Hi there</title><link>https://lxhan.github.io/work/</link><description>Recent content in Experience on Hi there</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 14:08:54 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lxhan.github.io/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Crave</title><link>https://lxhan.github.io/work/crave/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lxhan.github.io/work/crave/</guid><description>Food ordering service&amp;nbsp;¶ Location: Seoul, Korea (remote)
Position: Backend developer
What I did:
Designed and implemented the service architecture for a robust and scalable food ordering platform. Refactored the entire JavaScript codebase to TypeScript, enhancing the maintainability and performance of the application. Configured and managed a cloud infrastructure on AWS, leveraging tools like Docker, ECS, Lambda, CodeDeploy and CodePipeline for deployment and management of the backend services. Website: craveup.com</description></item><item><title>Techlabs</title><link>https://lxhan.github.io/work/techlabs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lxhan.github.io/work/techlabs/</guid><description> Dating service&amp;nbsp;¶ Location: Seoul, Korea
Position: Fullstack developer
What I did:
Successfully maintained the legacy PHP backend of a dating app, ensuring seamless user experiences. Assisted in migrating the backend to Kotlin, leveraging my experience in multiple programming languages. Developed data-driven dashboards to effectively monitor service metrics and improve overall performance. Website: nextmatch.kr
Tech stack:
PHP MySQL TypeScript React.js AWS Kotlin</description></item><item><title>Cemware</title><link>https://lxhan.github.io/work/cemware/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lxhan.github.io/work/cemware/</guid><description>Engineering Solution with Computing &amp;amp; Mathematics&amp;nbsp;¶ Location: Seoul, Korea
Position: Fullstack developer
What I did:
Contributed to the development of math learning tools in collaboration with KOFAC to improve students&amp;rsquo; academic performance. Refactored backend architecture from PHP to Golang to increase performance and handle high-load tolerance, resulting in improved user experience. Developed full-stack solutions using a variety of technologies including JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Angular, Vue.js, Node.js, Golang, and AWS. Website: cemware.</description></item><item><title>WM</title><link>https://lxhan.github.io/work/wm/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lxhan.github.io/work/wm/</guid><description>Web agency&amp;nbsp;¶ Location: Suwon, Korea
Position: Backend developer
What I did:
Developed the backend infrastructure for client web applications, ensuring robust and scalable solutions that met project requirements and deadlines. Utilized my expertise in Python and PHP to create efficient and reliable web scraping scripts, enabling the agency to efficiently gather valuable data and insights from a variety of sources. Maintained and optimized database systems, utilizing MySQL to ensure optimal performance and accuracy.</description></item><item><title>Bizhost</title><link>https://lxhan.github.io/work/bizhost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lxhan.github.io/work/bizhost/</guid><description> Hosting service&amp;nbsp;¶ Location: Seoul, Korea
Position: Backend developer
What I did:
Contributed to the upgrade of the hosting service&amp;rsquo;s PHP version from v4 to v5, ensuring compatibility with the latest technologies and improving performance. Assisted in the upgrade of the MySQL version from v4 to v5, resulting in enhanced database management capabilities. Website: bizhost.co.kr
Tech stack:
PHP MySQL</description></item><item><title>Two Number</title><link>https://lxhan.github.io/work/twonumber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:33:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lxhan.github.io/work/twonumber/</guid><description>Telecommunication company&amp;nbsp;¶ Location: Seoul, Korea
Position: Fullstack developer
What I did:
Designed and developed a user-friendly front-end application for new user onboarding, leveraging my expertise in HTML/CSS, JavaScript (jQuery), and PHP. Contributed to the streamlining of the onboarding process for new users, improving the overall user experience. Assisted in the migration of the existing backend codebase to a custom framework, demonstrating my ability to work with diverse technologies and effectively communicate with cross-functional teams.</description></item><item><title>Crim C&amp;M</title><link>https://lxhan.github.io/work/crim/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:33:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lxhan.github.io/work/crim/</guid><description> Web agency&amp;nbsp;¶ Location: Suwon, Korea
Position: Backend developer
What I did:
Developed scalable and robust back-end solutions for web applications serving various clients. Designed and implemented database schemas to support project requirements, while maintaining and optimizing existing databases. Managed the CI/CD pipeline, ensuring timely delivery of projects to clients with high quality standards. Website: crim.co.kr
Tech stack:
CakePHP MySQL</description></item><item><title>Ritz Club</title><link>https://lxhan.github.io/work/ritz/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lxhan.github.io/work/ritz/</guid><description> Web agency&amp;nbsp;¶ Location: Seoul, Korea
Position: Fullstack developer
What I did:
Developed and delivered custom web applications for clients in the wedding industry, meeting project requirements and deadlines. Contributed to the code refactoring process, resulting in improved performance, maintainability and overall project quality. Collaborated with the development team in the migration of the codebase to XpressEngine, providing a modern and scalable platform for future projects. Tech stack:
CentOS XpressEngine MySQL HTML/CSS JavaScript (jQuery)</description></item><item><title>Brand.uz</title><link>https://lxhan.github.io/work/branduz/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:33:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lxhan.github.io/work/branduz/</guid><description>Internship and my first job at web agency&amp;nbsp;¶ Location: Tashkent, Uzbekistan
Position: Frontend developer
What I did:
Developed and delivered web applications for clients with varying complexity levels using HTML/CSS, JavaScript (jQuery), PHP and MySQL. Improved performance of legacy projects by re-writing JavaScript code and optimizing images, leading to faster load times. Assisted with the integration of front-end elements into a custom PHP framework, showcasing technical skills and versatility. Website: brand.</description></item></channel></rss>